http://www.myweddingfavors.com/policies/privacy-policy

Continue Shopping
Save 20% | Use code MWFSALE20 | No Minimum Purchase - Click for Details and Exclusions
All Holidays
Personalized Holiday 4 oz. Mini Mason Mug Shot Glass with Lid
Modern Romance
Mr. & Mrs.
My Wedding Favors Privacy Policy
Thank you for shopping with MyWeddingFavors.com. Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the internet's vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence.We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how My Wedding Favors collects information from all end users of My Wedding Favors' internet services (the "Services"),those who access some of our Services but do not make a purchase ("Visitors") as well as those who make a purchase ("Customers"); what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Customers have concerning the collection and use of such information. My Wedding Favors requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.IntroductionMy Wedding Favors collects information in different ways from Visitors and customers who access the various parts of our Services. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.Data SecurityThe membership, bookstore and donations information you provide - including credit card information - is secured using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. We use this SSL technology to prevent such information from being intercepted and read as it is transmitted over the Internet. The encrypted data goes to a secure site where your information is stored on restricted-access computers located at restricted-access sites. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.Responses to Email InquiriesWhen Visitors or Customers send email inquiries to My Wedding Favors, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. My Wedding Favors does not share the return email address with any third party."Cookies" and Why My Wedding Favors Uses ThemA "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. My Wedding Favors may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. If you are a Customer, we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services for a better customer experience. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit non-My Wedding Favors web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies.Special CasesIt is the policy of My Wedding Favors not to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Customers in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to prohibit such unrelated uses. However, My Wedding Favors may disclose personal information about Visitors or Customers, if we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to operate the Services properly or to protect My Wedding Favors and our Members.Our website uses third party cookies from Google to assist us in gathering aggregated data about our website visitors through Google Analytics. We also use third-party cookies from Google for re marketing, which may show our ads on Google or other web properties on the Internet, based on your past visits to our website. You may opt-out of Google's re-marketing by visiting their Google Ads Settings page or the Network Adverting Initiative Opt Out Page.Public Forums and BlogsPlease remember that any information you may disclose in public areas of our Web sites or the internet in general, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.My Wedding Favors' Commitment to Children's PrivacyProtecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws.Revisions to This PolicyMy Wedding Favors reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted here and will only apply to information collected after any such change. By visiting our website you agree to accept any changes made to this policy.Where to Direct Questions About the My Wedding Favors Privacy PolicyIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, contact:My Wedding FavorsDirector of Customer Service2700 Breckinridge Blvd A, Duluth, GA  30096Phone toll free 1-866-942-1311Email: MyWeddingFavors@TheShopsat24seven.com
